Suddenly, an expedition!
Hello everyone!
My name is Waka Yasumori!
Please come in!
This is the Ikinari Expedition!
Today, we have Ms. Yasumori, the leader of the Ikinari Expedition.
Mr. Yasumori, the leader of the Ikinari Expedition, is here by himself.
After this, we were going to have Shinju-san, the leader of the Ikinari Expedition, come and take pictures with us.
We were going to take pictures together.
But today!
A little early, isn't it?
I had to call Mr. Yasumori.
By the time I called him up.
There's a reason why I called him out, of course.
Mr. Yasumori, as this year's expedition leader
By the time this video is released, it will be December.
It's already the end of this year, and I'd like to thank you for your hard work as expedition leader.
I'd like to thank you for your hard work.
I've prepared a little reward for you.
I have prepared it.
But, since we are an expedition team, we can't just give out free rewards.
Today, Mr. Yasumori is going to challenge a certain mission, and if he clears the mission, he will get a reward.
The mission is that Ms. Yasumori will come here later for a photo shoot, and during the shoot, she'll be with Pearl.
During the shoot, you see...
I'm going to ask you to eat all the candy I've given you without being detected.
What? You mean during the shoot?
That's right. If you can eat it secretly during the shoot, you're cleared.
If Pearl finds out...
What are you doing, Waka-chan? Are you eating something? or something?
If she notices, you're out.
I see.
Mission in candy!
Good luck with your young cruise.
Today, I'd like to introduce you to some snacks.
I'd like to introduce you to some snacks.
May I have a word with you?
We're on a level.
Let's start with this one.
Kalpas.
This one's not too hard.
I think I can do this.
Talking.
It's pretty loud.
It opens up a lot.
I think this is the next one.
This one.
It's like Jell-O.
It's delicious.
Jelly.
Dora Chocolate. It's so moist, it doesn't even make a sound.
I'm going to have to fake it.
Absolutely impossible. Absolutely impossible.
It's okay.
Absolutely impossible, because there's so much of it, it'll make your mouth water!
Crackle panic!
This one crackles in your mouth.
Absolutely impossible.
Absolutely impossible!
If you eat it when you're shirting, it's a little more painful.
Even if you're not shirting...
If it crackles in your mouth, you'll be fine.
That's the kind of person I am.
You just have to go with it.
I'm the kind of person who makes noises in my mouth.
Like, "I'm going to crackle a little today.
And if I finish all the sweets I've prepared.
If you eat them all, right?
What is your favorite candy?
It's also from the candy project.
Naka-Can
I prepared a box.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
No, no, no.
It's easy.
It's just a present.
I thought it was a Christmas present.
Of course it's yours if you clear it.
Are you sure? A box.
In case it's too easy to clear.
Yes, it's possible.
There's a chance you'll get the middle can easily.
I prepared one bonus stage.
I'll be on the offensive.
If you clear all of them...
If you clear all of them, and if there's still room...
This way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Keep thinking about it.
Tacosen.
I'll take one of these.
Not all of them, of course.
Of course. - One piece.
I'll give you another box of medium cans.
What?
Are you serious?
Yes, sir.
So please do your best to complete the mission.
Okay.
If you go to the octopus fight and fail, you get one box.
Oh!
I won't do without it.
Then I'll show you what I can do.
Why are you the captain this year?
That's right.
I'd like to shake hands with you in the name of the captain.
Please make sure this project succeeds.
Yes, I will.
And the fact that it's with Pearl...
That's right.
There's a chance she won't even notice. It's totally possible.
There's also the possibility that she's wondering what you're doing, but she's not going to tell you.
It's like they were aware but didn't say anything.
You can take advantage of that and still be okay with it.
If she doesn't say why she's eating sweets, it's the end.
Okay, we're not done with Pearl yet, so come back after this and get ready.
After we're done, we'll start the expedition, and then we'll get started.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go! Let's go!
I'm Waka Yasumori. This is Shinju Yoshii.
I'm Waka Yasumori and I'm Shinju Yoshii. Nice to meet you.
I'm Waka Yasumori and I'm Shinobu Yoshii. We're from the "Suddenly Expedition" group.
These two are here today, and I'd like them to do something for us.
Yes.
I have a project for you two. Do you write New Year's cards?
Do you write New Year's cards on postcards or do young people nowadays send them on line?
Yes, we met once, 5 or 6 years ago.
We sent each other handwritten notes.
Each one sent 8? We used to send each other messages. Now we don't do that anymore.
We send each other 8 handwritten New Year's cards.
We are planning to write New Year's greeting cards to e-beans and other stores in the e-beans building.
We hope you will write your own original New Year's card with your heart and soul!
Let's start writing.
Let's get started!
Let's start!
I don't know what to do.
This is the kind of test, right?
What? What?
Sense?
Why are you so bad at sense?
I don't think so.
Because there is a sense, a great sense.
I see. We've done this before, haven't we? We were together before.
What was it?
The sewing thing.
We did it here.
Sure, sure, sure. No, what? Don't worry about it. It's fine with Pearl. It's your personality.
Sure, sure. If we can get to the point where it's not just about taste.
This is how it's going to be. Yes, yes, if we do it this way, it will be fine.
I don't know what to do. We are working on the composition now.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to be pichin', this one.
I'm going to write seriously.
Sure thing.
Fast forward?
Hmm?
Fast forward.
What?
When this scene is happening.
This part?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure it's supposed to be cut.
He's not even talking.
I'm sure.
Well, have him write it down.
And isn't that pen you're holding thick? That's...
Isn't that a thick one? Much thicker.
Are you okay? That one.
You complain a lot, don't you?
No, I've only had two, haven't I? Not yet.
What's with the pen?
Isn't the footen low? On the contrary.
Hey.
It's a showdown between a lot of complaints and a low footen.
LOL!
Thank you for watching.
Are you okay?
No reply
No reply.
I'm fine.
Let's get a quick cutaway shot.
I can see it anyway.
Look, doesn't it look good? As if to say.
It looks like a doodle.
Oh, I see! Like that one, from Dragon Ball.
Yes, yes, that's the image.
Wow! That's what I'm talking about!
As expected of a shounen manga!
You're very kind, Yasumori-san.
No, it's natural.
No, you're kind, isn't it natural, even though it's funny?
No, it's to notice such pearls, such trifles
It's my role in life.
It's a heavy role.
I'll write that one down, too. It's like a ball.
Dragon balls?
Like balls?
What?
Like seven balls.
And then we'll scatter them around and put something in them.
Oh, that sounds good.
Nice to meet you.
You want to make it seven letters?
Yes, I do.
Why the balls... why?
You want to write letters inside the balls, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I see.
Because there are seven Dragon Balls.
Why... oh, I see.
Why?
He's never seen them.
You've never seen them?
You've never seen it?
I didn't think you'd see it.
I'm going to write it down now.
I can only imagine.
Akemashinju, isn't it?
Akemashinju.
As expected...
I'm so relaxed... so relaxed...
That's what I'm talking about!
Nice Akemashinju.
I want something like that.
Yasumo Ryu
You're hired, aren't you?
I'll draw a little here. Why don't you make a dragon with your face?
Yeah, that's good.
Like a dragon with a face.
A dragon with a face?
Yes, that's right.
That would be fun.
I might be able to do it. I might be able to draw it.
You think you can do it?
Yes, I think I can do it.
OK.
Then, let's draw it.
Hmmm...
Are you sleeping, Mr. Yasuho?
What's wrong?
You got a good idea?
Yes, I did.
I could imagine something.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And this way.
It's totally that, isn't it?
It's going to be good. I knew I wanted to make a wish come true.
I'd like to get an item from Mr. Ewenzi.
If it were you, what would you wish for?
If I had a Dragon Ball...
But only once. They say it's different.
But I guess I would wish for world peace.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
That's great.
If you put it that way, we're like sisters.
Because in Dragon Ball...
Why didn't anyone say that?
They only use it to bring people back to life.
Dragon Ball...
Except for Oolong, everyone else has that kind of wish, right?
Oolong is the only weird one.
I can't really say that in front of Pearl.
Right.
So, Dragon Ball is a wish-granting TV show?
From there?
From there? What did you say? No one should know.
That's from the first episode.
What did he say?
Dragon Ball.
What was your wish?
Dragon Ball wish? You mean in the story, right?
He's like a Super Saiyan.
You mean Goku?
Goku, Goku, Goku.
What was the first time?
Goku didn't say it first. He got told.
Maybe he was helping Bulma collect them.
Am I wrong? Oh yeah! I didn't know.
I didn't know.
Ifyou te
Ifyou tee
Hou ndao no thank you
It's okay.
It's okay. Are you okay?
Hardly.
Oh, I see. I turned his eyes into dragons.
Yes, I made them into dragon balls.
It's so good.
You know, I think I forgot to draw that one of yours, Kimitaka-san.
What?
Pearl Akiba?
Yes, I drew Pearl Akiba.
I drew it electronically.
I did it electronically.
Is it done?
Can I have Shinju-san introduce hers too?
It's so cute!
Her eyes are like dragon balls.
But actually...
I see... it's a reminder to come to Evin's and look for the seventh one.
I see... it means that you can find it at Evin's and your dream will come true.
I'm so moved. - You're moved? I'm so moved. You're that moved?
That's great. Thank you.
Can I see your stuff again? Yes!
Oh, my God, that's so good.
It's got personality.
So that completes the first one.
Okay, let's see the second one. Yes!
HMV is good, right? Yes, that's right.
Can I play background music like in HMV?
Background music? Tork's music? It's good, isn't it?
As long as it's something you can play. Really?
Okay, I can certainly get into the groove of it.
Service promotion!
What the hell is this time?
Oh, boy.
I'll read that too.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just sending it.
Laughs.
Laughing.
LOL!
Wonderful.
Oh, let this flow.
Hizusan-like, you know, you want to concentrate a little bit, you know, on the drawing.
Yeah.
No, it's a step down.
I want to concentrate a little bit inside.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes.
Oh!
Number two.
I'm counting on you.
h&km
Oh...
No, thank you.
Bonus time.
Now that was fun.
I think you made it to the top.
I got the hanging height, but...
But I haven't finished the work yet.
I haven't made any progress on the brushstrokes.
The second one.
Can I combine the two?
Yes! Like a heart.
Like a heart?
Okay, I'll draw this one.
So the temporary ones will be combined to make one picture.
I like it.
I like how you can't open the magic lid.
It's been about 5 years.
About five years.
Thank you.
It's funny.
It's getting cloudy.
I've got my meds for a second.
Are you guys okay?
Good night.
Thanks to your father, thanks to your mother, thanks to your mother,
Can I use the black one? Yes! Thank you.
What's up?
What's wrong?
What? What? What?
What?
Nothing on YouTube.
What's up?
YouTube.
It's okay. Let me know if you need anything.
Yeah, I know. Can I use black too?
Yeah, we're gonna do black and pink.
Okay.
What do you draw inside the heart?
What's inside the heart?
What's inside the heart? What do you think?
Like an H, an M, and a V.
And an M in the middle.
Say it again.
I'll write an H here and an M.
één 180 degrees uv.
Why?
Open it.
What is this?
Is today a one-hit wonder?
A one-hit wonder?
Hmm?
What's going on? Shinichi.
Hot, hot.
Let me get this straight.
What are you eating?
Hot, hot, hot.
What is that? I threw up.
What is that?
What did you say? Just now.
Are you doing a one-hit wonder today?
A one-hit wonder?
I thought you were very excited.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes...
Hot, hot, hot!
Oh, no, no, no!
Hot!
Hot, isn't it? It's hot, isn't it?
Did you feel something strange? Shin-san
Today's Yasumori-san
I feel nothing but discomfort.
Yes, yes
This is scary!
Yasumori-san's out!
Out!
What, what, what?
I can't stand it!
Moke-chan, I can't stand it!
You did your best!
But we made it. We made it to the shrimp 1000.
No, I didn't.
Pearl already noticed it before that.
I'm sure you'll notice, something's wrong.
Yes, I know.
But only from the crackling.
Did you hear it?
I heard the crackling.
That's why you're on so much medication.
I'll have to try not to.
Good luck with that.
I'm not supposed to say that.
You know, the crackle is what it is.
Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, good.
Good?
I'm glad it's a joke.
I'm glad it's just a funny thing.
Yeah, I thought there was something wrong with me.
Yeah, something's wrong with me.
Suddenly I want to crack up.
Oh, then I thought it was weird.
I thought it was... I thought it was...
So just pretend like you're not listening.
I see. You're filming it.
I think I'm cracking up.
I'm cracking up.
That's right, I've already been exposed.
I'll tell Pearl a little story.
Yes.
As a matter of fact, while I was writing this New Year's card today.
I had a mission for Yasumori-san.
What?
I gave it to him.
Yes, sir.
While I was writing the New Year's card.
"If you eat all the candy bars with me while I'm writing New Year's cards without being noticed, you'll be cleared.
If she eats all the candy with me, she's cleared?
That's right.
I gave it to Yasumori-san ahead of time.
Oh, I see.
Before Shinju-san came in today.
Actually, Yasumori-san came in early.
What?
We're already filming the opening.
And if you finish eating the candy without being noticed...
You'll get a prize if you finish eating it without being noticed.
Of course, we're going to make a New Year's greeting card video.
But in addition to that, Yasumori was challenging a mission.
I didn't notice that.
I've already eaten a lot of candy.
I eat a lot of candy.
Wasn't it unnatural that he dropped all the pens?
Oh, no, I just thought it was weird.
I really wanted you to help me, you know.
From Yasumori's point of view...
Oh, sorry.
While I was helping you...
While I'm helping you.
I have to have a Umaibo.
I was going to eat it, but...
But he didn't go through with it.
I was in a bit of a hurry.
I thought, "What should I do? If I miss this chance, I'll never have another chance to eat Umaibo.
Also, Yasumori Anno was dancing to the music.
Yasumori Anno was dancing to the music.
Yes, yes, yes.
That was funny, too, when I think about it.
When I think about it...
That's why I wondered if he was nervous about today's video.
I thought it was bad.
When you came in front of the camera, you were eating a Umaibo.
Wow.
Yeah, umami sticks make a lot of noise.
So I tried to eat them
I tried to eat it, but
but it was quite difficult.
Shinji, who insisted on stopping the song
He thought he had been stopped.
There's no way to eat the Umaibo now.
I think that was a nice touch.
It was a good workshop.
It's still hard to judge.
How far did you get?
If they found out at the Ebisen, we're all clear.
That's right.
But I thought it was medicine, the crackling.
I thought crackpot was a drug.
So, we're okay?
Are you sure?
Oh!
Just in case.
Yes!
You made it.
I really didn't notice.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I'll give you the prize just in case.
Are you sure?
Yes, Shinju-san will give it to you.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Well...
Mission accomplished, huh?
Yes, congratulations on completing the mission!
Thank you!
Yay!
Medium cans
A box of Yasome's favorite candy, Chuchi-Can!
You know, when he helped me open the cap
I was holding a Umaibo in my hand.
Because of the oil from the Umaibo...
I knew it.
That's what you thought?
Yeah!
But it's not like that now.
Really?
And the other thing that wasn't so great was...
The whole crew was laughing, including me.
Yeah!
You're laughing too much!
If they were laughing, I'd say, "What are you laughing at?
I started to get a little suspicious.
You're laughing too much!
This one...
No, that was... but...
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
I can't take it.
Nope.
I'm looking at Mr. Rasmori's...
Look at the video!
It's so funny!
Oh, my God!
Wait, it's super fun!
I'll just leave the mission in candy here for now.
It's so impulsive!
That's the end of it.
We'll continue with the New Year's greeting card video.
Oh, it's going to continue!
It's over.
To be continued
to be continued
continue
continued
continued this
continue this
this and that
next this
next
yes
Yes, ma'am.
Yay!
Correct. f sec.
It's like this.
But, yeah.
I know.
No, I don't.
Let's finish it.
Let's finish it up.
This is the place.
You know what?
What Kimitaka said...
What you said.
You're really ignoring what Kimitaka said.
Okay.
I was doing it because I was smokin'.
I was doing it!
Shin-san's H&V Festival New Year's card
Akema, Pearl, and best wishes!
I think this half of M and V match.
And here's mine.
There's something that looks like Heidi.
So cute!
Tell me!
Can you put these together to make one piece?
This is so cool!
I want this!
First time working together!
Wakaitsugu's
I'm sure you'll decorate it, won't you?
I'm so happy!
Festival day
Well, today we did two projects at the same time. First, Yasumori-san's mission in candy!
It turned out to be a success, but it wasn't a perfect accomplishment
Yes, but I learned a lot from it
What is it? Where can I use this?
Maybe to eat at school when the teacher isn't looking... or to make a fast lunch... as we used to do in the past.
I'm sure you could use this video as a reference. No, I can't do that.
I was more nervous than I was at the concert.
No, seriously, I was more nervous than at the concert. In a different way.
I'm sure we'll do it again in a different way...
I want Yasumori-san to try his hand at it, and Niitsu-san too
I want to do it! Let's make a mission
I like it I hope we can do something fun in the video
I'm looking forward to it
And the New Year's card... another project is to say thank you for your support in 2023
I'd like to thank you all for your support in 2023 and look forward to working with you again in 2024.
I asked E-BEANS and HMV to write a New Year's card for me.
I wrote them!
I'm so happy, I'm going to hang it up when it arrives!
I think it's going to be displayed at HMV's Tork's corner.
Please come check it out!
Well, that's all for today's exploration.
Thank you very much.
Please take a good rest.
I need to rest.
Yes, thank you very much.
See you soon